Prasanna Tuladhar

Web and mobile application developer (React, React Native)





Storgata 63, 0182, Oslo, Norway



+47 96708761



tuladharprasan@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/prasanna-tuladhar

Portfolio: www.prasannat.com

Profile

A performance-driven and goal-oriented individual with 2+ years of experience in the IT sector specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web and mobile projects. Well versed in numerous programming and development languages, possesses great organizational management and technological expertise, leadership skills, extensive communication skills, strong customer orientation, significant ability to work well in a team, and strong determination to perform excellent work.

Skill Highlights

- Front-end: HTML, CSS, Javascript (jQuery, React, React native)
- Back-end: Php (Wordpress, Laravel)
- Graphic designing: Adobe (Photoshop, Illustrator)
- Video Editing: Adobe Premiere
- UI/UX designing: Adobe InDesign
- Academic skills on Project Management, Data analytics, management control, consumer behavior.
- Creative design
- Time management
- Analytical thinking
- Organizational skills
- Planning
- Leadership
- Decision making
- Teamwork and collaboration

Experience

Application Developer (Web / Mobile) 07/03/2018 – 30/11/2020

I.Click Pvt.Ltd.
Dallu road, 44600 Kathmandu (Nepal)
http://iclicksms.com/

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Complete detailed programming and tasks for front-end (Javascript- jQuery, React and React native) as well as back-end (PHP- wordpress, Laravel) development.

Internship in Web Development 02/08/2017 – 09/12/2017 Sherpa Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

Thahity, 44600 Kathmandu (Nepal) http://www.sherpa-tech.com/

- Design and development of web applications (html, CSS, bootstrap framework, Php- Laravel).
- Develop api for api integration.
- Database design.
- Graphics designing (Adobe Photoshop, illustrator)

Education

Master's in Management Information System (MIS) 2020 – 2022

University of South-Eastern Norway (USN), Hønefoss, Ringerike, Norway

Degree in Bachelor's of Science in Computer Science and Information Technology 2013 – 2017

Tribhuvan University (Prime College), Kathmandu (Nepal)

Certifications

Certificate in Web Development Course 18/10/2016–15/03/2017

Student Project Nepal Computer Institute, Kathmandu (Nepal)